Lyrics from Genius & Gemini
Made by Randy
Ugh
Yeah
耶
Ugh
Look
听着
I done been through trials that most can't survive
我经历了大多数人无法幸存的磨难
I used the knife they put in my back to cut all my family ties
我用他们插在我背上的刀， 切断了我所有的家庭关系
Its hard when you start arm wrestling with the hands of time
当你开始与时间之手手腕时，会很艰难
But the time of death is the only thing you can't decide
但死亡的时间是你唯一无法决定的事情
gained some knowledge from reading a book
我从阅读一本书中获得了一些知识
I think this game these rap guys are as weak as they look
我认为这个圈子里的说唱歌手们，和他们看起来一样弱
I tell people I can't feed you but I can teach you to cook
我告诉人们我不能直接喂饱你，但我可以教你如何烹饪
Just know the cost of greed, its harder to eat when you're full
只需知道贪婪的代价，在你吃饱后，会更难进食（知足常乐）
Yeah, I'mma teach my daughter, that wisdom is hers
耶，我要教导我的女儿，智慧属于她
The lessons I learned from life came with a gift and a curse
我从生活中学到的教训，伴随着一份礼物和一份诅咒
The gift is you not feeling the pain that I felt at your age
礼物是你不会感受到我在你这个年纪所经历的痛苦
The curse is you don't get those lessons that can help with the pain
诅咒是你也因此错失了那些能帮助应对痛苦的经验
Yeah
耶
But sobriety wasn't sovereignty
但清醒并非就是主宰一切
In these verses I'm speaking logically
在这些歌词中，我正在有逻辑地表达
I had to learn to forgive them with no apology
我必须学会在没有道歉的情况下原谅他们
My humble beginnings I experienced, it taught me modesty
我经历过的卑微出身，教会了我谦逊
On the grind I never take a day off
在努力奋斗中，我从不休息
The struggle to get your people out the hood and stay strong
努力让你的族人摆脱贫困并保持坚强
I play the cards I was dealt, I only look to take charge
我打出我手里牌，我只想着掌控局面
But when they see you as a threat that's when they pull the race card
但当他们将你视为威胁时，他们就会打出种族牌
ery crypto investment I made couldn't outweigh the investment that I made in my
我做的每一笔加密货币投资，都比不上我对自身的投资
Or that I made in my health
或是我对我健康的投入
You put a wolf in sheep's clothing it's a price just to wear it
你让一只狼穿上羊皮，仅仅是穿上它就要付出代价
Got to be wise enough to know good advice when you hear it
你必须足够明智，才能听出良言忠告